Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Program recordings
  - 56. Clarinet Marmalade: The Clarinet in Early Jazz, Peplowski, Ken
    - Clarinet Marmalade: The Clarinet in Early Jazz, 1995-1998; 2 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 33)
      #12, 1995; #30, 1998
    - Clarinet Marmalade: The Clarinet in Early Jazz, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 57. All New Riverwalk All-Stars, Bagneris, Vernel; Carter, Benny; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Terry, Clark; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Linda Hopkins, Dick Hyman, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Clkark Terry and Benny Carter.
    - Riverwalk All-Stars. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-06-25; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - All New Riverwalk All-Stars, 1994; 1 audiocassette (Audio 24)
    - All New Riverwalk All-Stars. #3, 1994; 1 DAT (Audio 31)
    - Riverwalk Jazz All-Stars, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 58. Sax-Crazed: 100 Years of Saxophone Madness, Peplowski, Ken
    - Sax Stuff Show [cue sheet enclosed] Edited Production Master, Not Level Corrected, Not Based, 1994-03-01; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Sax-Crazed, 1994-1997; 6 audiocassettes (Audio 29)
      Sax Stuff: A Riverwalk Classic Jam 1994; Sax-Crazed: 100 Years of Saxophone; Sax-Crazed #9, 1997; Sax Stuff 1994; Rough Master 3/1/94
    - Sax-Crazed, 1994-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 31)
      #4, 1994; #9, 1997
    - Sax-Crazed: 100 Years of Saxophone Madness, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Sax-Crazed. #10, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 59. America's Funniest and Best Loved Jazz Stories, Giordano, Vince; Hampton, Lionel; McShann, Jay; Stein, Andy; Terry, Clark; Woods, Carol
    With guests Clark Terry, Lionel Hampton, Jay McShann, Vince Giordano, Andy Stein and Carol Woods. Title shortened in 2000 to America's Jazz Stories.
    - Jazz Anecdotes. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-06-24; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - America's Funniest and Best Loved Jazz Stories: The JCJB With Clark Terry and Jay McShann, 1994; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
    - America's Funniest and Best-Loved Jazz Stories, 1994-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 35, Audio 31)
      America's Funniest and Best-Loved Jazz Stories #5, 1994; America's Jazz Stories #35, 2000
    - America's Jazz Stories, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - America's Jazz Stories. #35, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 60. Battle of the Bands: San Antonio vs. New Orleans, Gibson, Banu; Glover, Savion; New Orleans Hot Jazz Orchestra.; Warfield, William
    The Jim Cullum Jazz Band versus The New Orleans Hot Jazz Orchestra, with guests Banu Gibson, William Warfield, and Savion Glover. Recorded live in 1994 at the Zaragoza Theater at the Fiesta Texas Park in San Antonio, Texas. See also Battle of the Bands commercial release (Riverwalk Vol. 4).
    - Battle of the Bands Outs Only, 1994-10-13; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - JCJB Battle of the Bands, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Battle of the Bands, 1994-1997; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
      JCJB With an All-Star Cast 1994; #18 Battle of the Bands: San Antonio vs. New Orleans 1997
    - Battle of the Bands: San Antonio vs. New Orleans, 1994-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 31)
      #6, 1994; #18, 1997
    - Battle of the Bands, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Battle of the Bands. #36, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Battle of the Bands. #33, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 61. Listeners' Choice and Riverwalk Favorites, Cocuzzi, John; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike; Wilber, Bob
    With guests Dick Hyman, Bob Wilber, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge and John Cocuzzi.
    - Listener's Choice. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-08-24; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Listener's Choice and Riverwalk Favorites, 1994; 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - Listeners' Choice and Riverwalk Favorites. #10, 1994; 1 DAT (Audio 31)
  - 62. Riverwalk, Live From Manhattan '94: The Music of Jelly Roll, King Oliver, and The New Orleans Rhythm Kings, Burrell, Terry; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Dick Hyman and Terry Burrell. Recorded live from the 92nd Street Y in New York City.
    Morton, Jelly Roll, d. 1941; New Orleans Rhythm Kings (1922-1925).; New Orleans Rhythm Kings (1934-1935).; Oliver, King, 1885-1938
    - Live From Manhattan. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-09-14; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
    - Riverwalk, Live From Manhattan '94. #14, 1994; 1 DAT (Audio 31)
  - 63. Empress of The Blues: The Life and Music of Bessie Smith, Chapman, Topsy
    With guest Topsy Chapman. See also commercial release The Bessie Smith Story: Bessie and The Blues (Riverwalk Vol. 3).
    Smith, Bessie, 1894-1937
    - Bessie Smith Show Playback Master, 1994-09-13; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 11)
    - Empress of the Blues, 1994-1997; 4 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      1994; 1995; #19, 1997
    - Empress of The Blues, 1994-1997; 3 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 32, Audio 33)
      #16, 1994; #20, 1995; #19, 1997
    - Empress of The Blues: The Life and Music of Bessie Smith, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Empress of The Blues. #40, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Empress of The Blues. #11, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Empress of The Blues. #14, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 64. Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues, Terry, Clark; Warfield, William
    With guests William Warfield and Clark Terry.
    - Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues [cue sheet enclosed] Edited Production Master, Not Level Corrected, Not BASED, 1994-09-15; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
    - Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues, 1994; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 29)
    - Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues, 1994-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 35, Audio 31)
      #19, 1994; #34, 2000
    - Spirituals, Hymns and Blues, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Spirituals, Hymns and The Blues. #34, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 65. Postcard From San Antonio Christmas Special '94, Campanas de Ameand#769;rica (Musical group).; Gibson, Banu; Glover, Savion
    With guests Savion Glover, Banu Gibson and the Campanas de América mariachi band.
    - Postcard From San Antonio, '94 Christmas Show. Copy of DAT Broadcast Master, Pgm. #25, 1994; 1 audiocassette (Audio 28)
    - Postcard From San Antonio. San Antonio Christmas Special, 1994-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 36)
      #25, 1994; #51, 2000
    - Postcard From San Antonio. #51, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Postcard From San Antonio. #51 ["Bad disk?"], 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 66. Texas Roots in Jazz and Blues: Lone Star Boogie Woogie and Swing, Ogilvie, Brian
    With guest Brian Ogilvie.
    - Texas Roots in Jazz and Blues [cue sheet enclosed] Edited Production Master, Not Level Corrected, Not BASED, 1994-09-14; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
    - Texas Roots Playback Master, 1994-09-08; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 11)
    - Texas Roots, 2 audiocassettes (Audio 29)
      1994; #7, 1997
    - Texas Roots, 1994-2001; 3 DATs (Audio 37, Audio 31, Audio 32)
      #17, 1994; #7, 1997; #24, 2001
    - Texas Roots in Jazz and Blues, 1994; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Texas Roots in Jazz and Blues. #24, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 67. Manhattan Jam '94, Burrell, Terry; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Dick Hyman and Terry Burrell.
    - Manhattan Jam. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-11-10; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 12)
    - Riverwalk Concert; Riverwalk Radio Show. GBH Mobile., 1994-07-19; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 135)
    - Manhattan Jam, 1994-1997; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 27)
      Riverwalk New York '94 Show 7/19/94; Copy of DAT Broadcast Master, Pgm. #22, 1994; #6, 1997
    - Manhattan Jam, 1994-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 32)
      Manhattan Jam '94 #22, 1994; #6, 1997
  - 68. Jazz Legends: New Stories and Great Performances, Barnard, Bob; Chapman, Topsy; Davern, Kenny; Grosz, Marty; Stein, Andy; Terry, Clark
    With guests Andy Stein, Marty Grosz, Topsy Chapman, Bob Barnard, Kenny Davern and Clark Terry.
    - Jazz Legends. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-11-25; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 12)
    - Jazz Legends, 1994-1997; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 26)
      Copy of DAT Broadcast Master Pgm. #24, 1994; 1997
    - Jazz Legends, 1994-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 33)
      #24, 1994; #24, 1997
  - 69. Prez and Lady Day: A Tribute to the Music of Billie Holiday and Tenor Saxophonist Lester Young, Chapman, Topsy
    With guest Topsy Chapman.
    Holiday, Billie, 1915-1959; Young, Lester, 1909-1959
    - Prez and Lady Day: Lester Young and Billie Holiday [cue sheet enclosed] Original Production Master, 1995-02-07; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 13)
    - Prez and Lady Day, 1995-02-07; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 13)
    - Prez and Lady Day, 1995-1997; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
      Prez and Lady Day, With Topsy Chapman 2/7/95; Prez and Lady Day 1995; #16, 1997
    - Prez and Lady Day: A Tribute to Musical Soulmates Lester Young and Billie Holiday, 1995-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 31)
      #5, 1995; #16 Safety Dub, 1997
    - Prez and Lady Day, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Prez and Lady Day. #6, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 70. Riverwalk Jam, Chapman, Topsy; Payton, Nicholas
    With guests Topsy Chapman and Nicholas Payton.
    - Riverwalk Jam with Topsy C and Nicholas Payton [cue sheet enclosed] Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1995-02-08; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 13)
    - Riverwalk Classic Jam. JCJB with Topsy Chapman and Nicholas Payton, 1995-02-08; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
    - Riverwalk Classic Jam, with Topsy Chapman. Pulled From DAT, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 71. Louis Armstrong In the '30s: A Tribute to the Life and Music of Armstrong in the '30s, Payton, Nicholas
    With guest Nicholas Payton.
    - 1930 HRs from Armstrong, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Louis Armstrong [cue sheet enclosed], 1995-02-09; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 13)
    - Louie Armstrong In the '30s. Original Production Master [cue sheet enclosed], 1995-02-09; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 14)
    - Louie In the '30s Outs, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 14)
    - Louis Armstrong in the 30's, 1995-1998; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 27)
      2/9/95; #9, 1998
    - Louis Armstrong in the 30's, 1995-1998; 2 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 31)
      #1, 1995; #9, 1998
    - Louis Armstrong In the '30s, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Louis Armstrong In the '30s. #4, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Louis Armstrong In the '30s. #28, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 72. Bix and Hoagy: Midwestern Romantics of the Jazz Age, Gibson, Banu
    Beiderbecke, Bix, 1903-1931; Carmichael, Hoagy, 1899-1981
    - Bix and Hoagy. Original Production Master [cue sheet enclosed], 1995-04-18; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 14)
    - Bix and Hoagy Outs, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 14)
    - Bix and Hoagy, 1995-1998; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
      Office Dub 4/18/95; #4 1998
    - Bix and Hoagy, 1995-1999; 3 DATs (Audio 34, Audio 33, Audio 31)
      #2, 1995; #4, 1998; #46, 12/1999
    - Bix and Hoagy, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Bix and Hoagy. #46, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 73. The Boogie Woogie Beat: Rompin' Stompin' Rhythm, Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    - Boogie Woogie Beat Fall Funder, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Boogie Woogie Beat with Dick Hyman [cue sheet enclosed] Unedited Master, 1995-04-19; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 14)
    - Boogie Woogie Beat, 1995-04-19; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 14)
    - Boogie Woogie Beat, 1995-1998; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
      4/19/1995; #23 1998
    - Boogie Woogie Beat, 1995-2001; 5 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 33, Audio 32, Audio 37)
      #3, 1995; #26, 1996; #23, 1998; #3, 2002; Safety 2002
    - Boogie Woogie Beat, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Boogie Woogie Beat. #3, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 74. March of the Bobcats: A Tribute of Trumpeter Yank Lawson, Haggart, Bob; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    Bob Crosby's Bobcats (Musical group).; Lawson, Yank
    - Tribute to Yank Lawson Warm Up Tunes. Big Crash From China; Old Spinnin' Wheel; Come Back Sweet Papa; Lazy Mood, 1995-04; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 14)
    - Five Point Blues: The Legacy of Yank Lawson, 1995-07-15; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 15)
    - March of the Bobcats, 1995; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 27)
      Jazz on the Radio #15; March of the Bobcats 1995
    - March of the Bobcats, 1995-2001; 3 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 36, Audio 35)
      #4, 1995; [#50] 12/1999; #21, 2001
    - March of the Bobcats, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - March of the Bobcats. #21, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 75. From Tailgate to Swing: History of the Jazz Trombone, Barrett, Dan; Gibson, Banu
    - Jazz Trombone [cue sheet enclosed] Unedited Master, 1995-04-18 - 1995-04-19; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 14)
    - Jazz Trombone. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1995-07-14; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 15)
    - From Tailgate to Swing, 1995-1997; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      Office Dub 1995; 4/18/19/95; #21 1997
    - From Tailgate to Swing, 1995-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 33)
      #6, 1995; #21, 1997
    - From Tailgate to Swing, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - From Tailgate to Swing. #52, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 76. Riverwalk All-Stars 1995, Barrett, Dan; Chapman, Topsy; Gibson, Banu; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Payton, Nicholas; Peplowski, Ken; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Banu Gibson, Nicholas Payton, Topsy Chapman, Joe Williams, Dick Hyman, Dan Barrett and Ken Peplowski.
    - Riverwalk All-Stars, 1995; 1 audiocassette (Audio 28)
    - Riverwalk All-Stars, 1995-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 35, Audio 32)
      Riverwalk All-Stars 1995 #15; 1995; Riverwalk Jazz All-Stars #37, 2000.
    - Riverwalk Jazz All-Stars. #15, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Riverwalk All Stars. #37, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 77. Live From The West Coast: The Jim Cullum Jazz Band in concert at Stanford University, Part 2
    see Stanford recordings 1995
    Stanford Jazz Workshop.
    - Live From The West Coast, 1995; 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - Live From The West Coast, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 78. Show Boat: An Original Jazz Transcription, Christopher, Evan; Hammerstein, Oscar, 1895-1960; Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945; Warfield, William
    With guests William Warfield and Evan Christopher. New version created 2006 with same title.
    Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945. Show boat
    - Showboat Outtakes, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 16)
    - Show Boat, 1995-09-11; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 16)
    - Showboat. Original Production Master, 1995-09-11; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 16)
    - Showboat, 1995-1998; 5 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
      1995; 12/1/95; 9/11/95; #24, 1998
    - Showboat, 1996-2002; 5 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 38, Audio 33, Audio 35)
      #16, 1996; #24, 1998; #20, 2000; #38, 2002 [note: printed cover indicates #38 is Sweet Ballads and Red Hot Pianos, but label on DAT says Show Boat]; #38 Safety, 2002
    - Show Boat, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Show Boat. #20, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Show Boat. #38, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Show Boat. #11, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Show Boat. #49, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Show Boat. #50, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 79. The Magic of Jerome Kern, Christopher, Evan; Warfield, William
    With guests William Warfield and Evan Christopher.
    Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945
    - Jerome Kern, 1995-09-11; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 15)
    - Jerome Kern Production Master, 1995-09-11; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 15)
    - Magic of Jerome Kern. Original Production Master, 1995-11-27; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 16)
    - Magic of Jerome Kern, 1995; 4 audiocassettes (Audio 27)
      Test Cassette 12/1/95; 9/11/95; etc.
    - Magic of Jerome Kern, 1996-2000; 3 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 35)
      #17, 1996; #24, 2000; Original Master 2000
    - Magic of Jerome Kern, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Magic of Jerome Kern: A Tribute. #24, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 80. Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule, Gibson, Banu; Glover, Savion; Hinton, Milt; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Terry, Clark; Wilber, Bob; Woods, Carol
    With guests Carol Woods, Clark Terry, Milt Hinton, Bob Wilber, Dick Hyman, Savion Glover and Banu Gibson. 2005 version aired as "Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule: Joyful Jazz for the Holidays." See also commercial release Hot Jazz For A Cool Yule (Riverwalk Vol. 5).
    - Christmas Show. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1995; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 16)
    - Christmas Misc., 1995; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 16)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule: 'Tis The Season To Be Jammin', 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule, 1995-1997; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 26)
      1995; Rough Edit; 1997
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule, 1996-1998; 3 DATs (Audio 34, Audio 33, Audio 32)
      #25, 1996; #25, 1997; #36, 1998
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule, 1995; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule. #50, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule. #49, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule: Joyful Jazz for the Holidays. #50, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule: Joyful Jazz For The Holidays. #50, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Hot Jazz for a Cool Yule: Joyful Jazz For The Holidays. #50, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 81. Fireworks On The 4th!, Bagneris, Vernel; Glover, Savion; Haggart, Bob; Hampton, Lionel; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Peplowski, Ken; Terry, Clark; Walbridge, Mike; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Linda Hopkins, Lionel Hampton, Vernel Bagneris, Bob Haggart, Clark Terry, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Savion Glover, Ken Peplowski and Dick Hyman. 2000 broadcast titled "Fireworks: Red, Hot and Blues." See also commercial release Fireworks! Red Hot and Blues (Riverwalk Vol. 6).
    - Fireworks! Red Hot and Blues. #1, 1998; 1 audiocassette (Audio 25)
    - Fireworks On The 4th!, 1996-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 35, Audio 32)
      Fireworks On The 4th! #1, 1996; Fireworks: Red, Hot and Blues: #1, 1998; #33, 2000
    - Fireworks: Red, Hot and Blues, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Fireworks: Red, Hot and Blues. #33, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 82. Cole Porter and Irving Berlin: Music Made In America, Ferro, Nina
    With guest Nina Ferro.
    Berlin, Irving, 1888-1989; Porter, Cole, 1891-1964
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin [cue sheet enclosed], 1996-04-03; 3 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" Ampex 456 (Audio 18)
    - Porter - Berlin Show. Original Production Master, Unedited [cue sheet enclosed], 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 18)
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin, 1996; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 24, Audio 25)
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin, 1996-1999; 2 DATs (Audio 34, Audio 32)
      #2, 1996; #1, 1999
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin. #1, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Cole Porter and Irving Berlin. #5, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 83. Over the Rainbow: The Music of Harold Arlen, Ferro, Nina; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Nina Ferro and Dick Hyman.
    Arlen, Harold, 1905-1986
    - Over The Rainbow: Dick Hyman, piano; Nina Ferro, vocals [cue sheet enclosed] Original Production Master, Unedited, 1996-04-01; 3 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 17)
    - Over The Rainbow, 1996-04-01; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" 3M 986, 966 (Audio 17)
    - Over the Rainbow, 2 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
      Office Copy Only 1996; 4/1/96 Show
    - Over the Rainbow, 1996-1999; 2 DATs (Audio 34, Audio 32)
      #3, 1996; #14, 1999
    - Over the Rainbow, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Over the Rainbow. #14, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 84. Remembering Count Basie, Terry, Clark; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Joe Williams and Clark Terry.
    Basie, Count, 1904-1984
    - Remembering Count Basie. #4, 1996; 1 DAT (Audio 32)
  - 85. Remembering Chicago Jazz, Cheatham, Doc; Hinton, Milt; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Doc Cheatham, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Milt Hinton and Dick Hyman.
    - Remembering Chicago Jazz. #5, 1996; 1 DAT (Audio 32)
  - 86. Playing With Fire: An Original Composition, San Jose Symphony.
    The JCJB in concert with the San Jose Symphony Orchestra.
    - Playing With Fire, 1997; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
      Frost Amphitheatre 7/21/96; #15 1997
    - Playing With Fire, 1996-1997; 2 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 32)
      #22, 1996; #15, 1997
    - Playing With Fire: An Original Composition, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Playing With Fire, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 87. Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop (Part 1), Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Leon Oakley and Mike Walbridge. 1999 broadcast titled "King Oliver and Company, Live From the Stanford Jazz Workshop." See also1996 Stanford recordings.
    Oliver, King, 1885-1938; Stanford Jazz Workshop.
    - Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop (Part 1), 1996; 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop, 1996-1999; 2 DATs (Audio 34, Audio 32)
      Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop. #12, 1996; King Oliver and Company, Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop. #29, 1999
    - King Oliver and Company. Stanford Jazz Workshop, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - King Oliver and Company, Live From the Stanford Jazz Workshop. #29, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Stanford: King Oliver. #31, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 88. Stanford Jazz Workshop 1996 (Part 2), Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Leon Oakley and Mike Walbridge. 1999 broadcast aired as "Turk and Lu: West Coast Giants of Jazz, Live From the Stanford Jazz Workshop." See also 1996 Stanford recordings.
    Murphy, Turk; Watters, Lu; Stanford Jazz Workshop.
    - Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop (Part 2), 1996; 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop Part II. Turk and Lu, 1996; 2 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 34)
      #21, 1996; #31, 1999
    - Turk and Lu: Stanford Jazz Workshop, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Turk and Lu: West Coast Giants of Jazz, Live From The Stanford Jazz Workshop. #31, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 89. Gershwin and Gershwin: 100 Years of Rhythm, Ferro, Nina
    With guest Nina Ferro. Title changed for 2001 rebroadcast to "Brother Can You Spare A Rhyme: The Story of George and Ira Gershwin."
    - Gershwin and Gershwin: 100 Years of Rhythm, 1995-1996; 2 folders, 2 computer disks (Box 102)
    - Gershwin and Gershwin. Original Production Master. [cue sheet enclosed], 1996-04-02; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 17)
    - Gershwin and Gershwin, 1996-04-02; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 2" 3M 966 (Audio 17, Audio 18)
    - Gershwin and Gershwin, 1996; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      Office Dub 1996; 4/2/96
    - Gershwin, 1996-2001; 2 DATs (Audio 37, Audio 32)
      Gershwin and Gershwin. #23, 1996; Spare A Dime, The Gershwin Story #38 Safety 2001
    - Brother Can You Spare A Rhyme: George and Ira Gershwin, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Brother Can You Spare A Rhyme: The Story of George and Ira Gershwin. #38, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 90. Harlem Rhapsody: A Celebration of Music and Poetry From the Harlem Renaissance, Bagneris, Vernel; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Warfield, William
    With guests William Warfield, Vernel Bagneris, and Dick Hyman.
    Harlem Renaissance
    - Harlem Rhapsody, 1996; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      9/9/96; Test Cassette #20 12/9/96; 1996
    - Harlem Rhapsody, 1996-2002; 2 DATs (Audio 38, Audio 32)
      #20, 1996; Black History Month 2002
    - Harlem Rhapsody, 1996; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Harlem Rhapsody. Special, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Harlem Rhapsody. #8, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 91. From Lenox Avenue To Broadway: How the Music of Harlem Influenced Broadway, Bagneris, Vernel; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Dick Hyman and Vernel Bagneris.
    Musicals
    - Lenox to Broadway, 1996-09-10; 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - From Lenox Avenue To Broadway, 1996-2000; 2 DATs (Audio 35, Audio 32)
      #18, 1996; #7, 2000